A Guide to the Records of the President's Office, Virginia Union University 1934-1999
Archives and Special Collections Department, L. Douglas Wilder Library, Virginia Union University
Archives and Special Collections Department, L. Douglas Wilder Library, Virginia Union University
The Records of the President's Office, Virginia Union University 1934-1999
Archives and Special Collections Department, L. Douglas Wilder Library, Virginia Union University
AR-0009
Administrative Information
Access
There are files relating to students' standing with the university - financial and academic - so that this collection should be considered restricted depending on the researcher's intended use. It is probably advisable that the university's legal counsel be consulted for any outside research requests
Scope and Content Information
These records reflect the administration of the university as well as the president's outreach activities such as alumni relations and speaking engagements.
The presidents of the University have been as follows:
Dr. Malcolm MacVicar (1899-1904)
Dr. George R. Hovey (1905-1918)
Dr. William J. Clark (1919-1941)
Dr. John M. Ellison (1941-1955)
Dr. Samuel D. Proctor (1955-1960)
Dr. Thomas H. Henderson (1960-1970)
Dr. Allix B. James (1970-1979)
Dr. Dorothy N. Cowling, (acting 1979)
Dr. David T. Shannon(1979-1985)
Dr. S. Dallas Simmons (1985-1999)
Dr. Bernard W. Franklin (1999- )
Much of the collection consists of memos and letters to and from the president.
Arrangement
Arrangement
The files are arranged alphabetically by subject.
Organization
Series I Administration of Dr. Allix B. James 1970-1979: James started working at Virginia Union University in 1947 as a Bible instructor. He was promoted to Dean of Students, then Dean of the Graduate School of Religion. He was Vice President under Dr. Henderson before being appointed President when Henderson died in 1970.
During his tenure, James oversaw many accomplishments, including the establishment of a vigorous corporate gift program, the most notable being a $2 million donation from Mr. and Mrs. Sydney Lewis matched by the Ford Foundation on a challenge from Lewis. Other corporate donors included Rockefeller, Lilly, Mellon, Phillip Morris and Kellogg. These gifts allowed renovations to the aging campus facilities among other things. The old Department of Commerce was upgraded and named the Sydney Lewis School of Business Administration, achieving full accreditation in the process.
Coburn Hall burned in James' first year as President; it wouldn't get rebuilt until Dr. Simmons' administration. Dave Robbins was appointed basketball coach under James, creating some controversy because he was not African-American. This contention was set aside, however, when Robbins coached the Panthers to a record number of championship wins.
Two Homecoming programs in the James years featured actors Bill Cosby, Sidney Poitier and TV "Mission Impossible's" Greg Morris. Community Learning Week was established as a city-wide celebration after beginning as a university holiday to mark the assassination of Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Upward Bound, a preparatory program for college-bound youths, was started on campus during James' administration.
Dr. James stepped down from the presidency in 1979 and took a year's sabbatical leave. He returned as a full professor of theology and retired completely from Virginia Union University in 1993.
Series II Administration of Dr. S. Dallas Simmons 1985-1999: Simmons was known as a businessman credited with turning around the university's $6 million deficit and eliminating it within 6 years. He was only the second president of Virginia Union University who was not a clergyman. The first was Dr. Henderson. Before coming to Virginia Union University in 1985, Simmons was president of St. Paul's College in Lawrenceville. He had taught business at North Carolina Central University previously, and holds a Ph.D. from Duke University.
Besides pulling the university from the brink of bankruptcy, Simmons is most notably credited with the construction of the university's first library building. The L. Douglas Wilder Library was opened in 1997.
Other accomplishments, according to a full-color brochure "A Decade of Achievement," include reinstating 11 endowed scholarships and establishing 57 new ones, rebuilding Coburn Hall finally after it burned in 1970, bringing a police academy to campus in a cooperative effort with the Richmond police, bringing the headquarters of the Baptist General Convention to campus, tripling the university's overall endowment, and earning the highest auditors' ratings after establishing a strict internal accounting system and hiring 4 CPAs to staff the university accounting office
Simmons resigned in 1999.
Series III Administration of Dr. William J. Clark 1919-1941: Clark was the third president of Virginia Union University and the president of the longest tenure. He was a professor of church history and theological instruction at Virginia Union University before becoming president. During his administration, the university merged with Hartshorn Memorial College, a sister college adjacent to the Virginia Union University campus. The Hartshorn property was sold to balance the Virginia Union University books which suffered during the Depression. See Virginia Union Bulletin, Centennial Issue, June 1965, "A Century of Service to Education and Religion" for overview of Clark's administration.
Contents List
- Series I
  - American Baptist Churches 1973-1976 (Box-folder 1:1)
  - American Baptist Churches 1973-1976 (Box-folder 1:2)
  - Applications for positions Jan 1976 (Box-folder 1:3)
  - Applications for positions Jan 1976 (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Association of American Colleges 1975-1976 (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Association of Governing of Universities and Colleges 1971-1977 (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Association of Governing of Universities and Colleges 1971-1977 (Box-folder 1:7)
  - B (Box-folder 1:8)
  - Consultants- James H. Rhett (Box-folder 1:9)
  - Consultants- Steve McLean (Box-folder 1:10)
  - Consultants- Lawson and Williams (Box-folder 1:11)
  - College Service Bureau 1969-1971 (Box-folder 1:12)
  - College Service Bureau 1969-1971 (Box-folder 1:13)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia 1968-1977 (Box-folder 1:14)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia 1968-1977 (Box-folder 1:15)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia 1969-1977 (Box-folder 1:16)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia 1969-1977 (Box-folder 1:17)
  - CIAA- Tournament 1977 (Box-folder 2:1)
  - CIAA- Tournament 1977 (Box-folder 2:2)
  - CIAA 1972-1976 (Box-folder 2:3)
  - CIAA 1972-1976 (Box-folder 2:4)
  - CIAA 1972-1976 (Box-folder 2:5)
  - CIAA 1972-1976 (Box-folder 2:6)
  - CIAA 1972-1976 (Box-folder 2:7)
  - F 1975-1977 (Box-folder 2:8)
  - Fund of Renewal 1974-1976 (Box-folder 2:9)
  - Founder's Day 1978 Feb 10 (Box-folder 2:10)
  - Founder's Day Report for Gifts and Grants (Box-folder 2:11)
  - G 1975-1978 (Box-folder 2:12)
  - Gifts and Grants July-Dec 1977 (Box-folder 2:13)
  - Governor's Office (Box-folder 2:14)
  - Gifts and Grants Jan-Dec 1978 (Box-folder 3:1)
  - General Study Asst. VP for Academic Affair (Box-folder 3:2)
  - General Study Asst. VP for Academic Affair (Box-folder 3:3)
  - Higher Education and National Affairs (Box-folder 3:4)
  - Holladay J. Douglas Re; Young Life (Box-folder 3:5)
  - H 1975-1978 (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Inventory of Resources Va. Union 1967 1967 (Box-folder 3:7)
  - J 1975-1978 (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Joan Brooks (Box-folder 3:9)
  - Lawson and Willams Central Record Files (Box-folder 3:10)
  - Music Department 1972-1975 (Box-folder 3:11)
  - Music Department 1972-1975 (Box-folder 3:12)
  - Music Department 1972-1975 (Box-folder 3:13)
  - McLean, Dr. E. Lee or Stephan McLean (Box-folder 3:14)
  - M 1972-1977 (Box-folder 3:15)
  - NAIA (National Association of Intercollegiate Athlethics) (Box-folder 4:1)
  - NAFEO (Box-folder 4:2)
  - NAFEO (Box-folder 4:3)
  - NAFEO Higher Education (Box-folder 4:4)
  - NAFEO Meeting 1978 Feb 28 (Box-folder 4:5)
  - NAFEO Meeting 1977 Aug 2 (Box-folder 4:6)
  - NAFEO Meeting 1977 July 24 (Box-folder 4:7)
  - NAFEO (Box-folder 4:8)
  - N 1975-1978 (Box-folder 4:9)
  - Prospective Faculty and Staff 1974-1976 (Box-folder 4:10)
  - Prospective Faculty and Staff 1974-1976 (Box-folder 4:11)
  - Prospective Faculty and Staff 1974-1976 (Box-folder 4:12)
  - Prince Edward Free School Ass. (Box-folder 4:13)
  - Prince Edward Free School Ass. (Box-folder 4:14)
  - Prince Edward Free School Ass. (Box-folder 4:15)
  - Programs (Box-folder 4:16)
  - Recruitment Kenneth Saffold (Box-folder 5:1)
  - Recruitment Kenneth Saffold (Box-folder 5:2)
  - Requisitions 1972 (Box-folder 5:3)
  - Requisitions 1972 (Box-folder 5:4)
  - Requisitions 1972 (Box-folder 5:5)
  - Requisitions 1974-1975 (Box-folder 5:6)
  - Requisitions 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5:6)
  - Requisitions 1973-1974, Part 2 Feb-Jun 1974 (Box-folder 5:8)
  - Students Accepted 1972-1973 (Box-folder 3:9)
  - Students Accepted 1973-1974 (Box-folder 3:10)
  - Students Accepted 1975-1977 (Box-folder 3:11)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Va. (Box-folder 5:12)
  - S 1975-1976 (Box-folder 5:13)
  - Sponsored Programs (Box-folder 5:14)
  - School of Theology Jan 1976- Dec 1978 (Box-folder 5:15)
  - School of Theology Jan 1976- Dec 1978 (Box-folder 5:16)
  - School of Theology Jan 1976- Dec 1978 (Box-folder 5:17)
  - Sidney Lewis School of Business dedicated 1973 Nov 2 (Box-folder 6:1)
  - Sidney Lewis School of Business dedicated 1973 Nov 2 (Box-folder 6:2)
  - Sidney Lewis School of Business dedicated 1973 Nov 2 (Box-folder 6:3)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools 1963 Jun 10 (Box-folder 6:4)
  - Southern Association (Box-folder 6:5)
  - Southern Association Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box-folder 6:6)
  - Southern Association Reports for last ten years (Box-folder 6:7)
  - Southern Association Special Study (Box-folder 6:8)
  - Southern Association 55th (Box-folder 6:9)
  - Southern Association Reports 1956-1957 (Box-folder 6:10)
  - Southern Association Reports (Box-folder 6:11)
  - Southern Association 1954 (Box-folder 6:12)
  - Theresa Smith (Box-folder 6:13)
  - Time and Attendance (Box-folder 6:14)
  - Agnes Fields Winston (Box-folder 6:15)
  - Xerox Charges 1974-1975 (Box-folder 6:16)
  - To Set at Liberty, School of Theology catalogue (Box 7)
  - Directory of Community Services n.d. (Box 7)
  - Annual Report of the Executive Secretary, Baptist General Convention of Virginia 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - 73rd Commencement program 1972 (Box 7)
  - The Crisis Jan 1972 (Box 7)
  - The Crisis Dec 1971 (Box 7)
  - Negro History Bulletin Dec 1971 (Box 7)
  - Brief Amicus Curiae of Council of Independent Colleges in Virginia, Andrew P. Miller v. David B. Ayres Jr., in the Supreme Court of Virginia, Record Nos. 8009, 8010 (Box 7)
  - Women in Medicine, Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority Heritage Series #4 1971 (Box 7)
  - Directory of Richmond, Virginia public schools 1969-1970 (Box 7)
  - A Guide to the Richmond Public Schools 1971-1972 (Box 7)
  - A Guide to the Richmond Public Schools 1972-1973 (Box 7)
  - University of Richmond Annual Report of the President 1971 (Box 7)
  - Program, 2nd Annual Joint Session of Bethany Baptist Association and Its Allied Bodies (Box 7)
  - An Do, V.U.U. Poetry 1970 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin of Virginia Union University Apr 1971 (Box 7)
  - "People Who..." Richmond Public Schools brochure 1972 (Box 7)
  - University of Richmond Annual Report of the Treasurer 1972 (Box 7)
  - Analysis of Enrollment, Student Financial Aid and Current Fund Revenue and Expenditures of Virginia Private Colleges and Universities 1970-1972 (Box 7)
  - The Higher Education Act of 1965 as Amended Title III, Strengthening Developing Institutions, Awards 1972 (Box 7)
  - School of Theology Bulletin and Catalogue 1969-1971, 2 copies (Box 7)
  - From Isolation to Mainstream, Problems of the Colleges Founded for Negroes Feb 1971 (Box 7)
  - White House Staff Mess, menu n.d. (Box 7)
  - Community Involvement Program, Parent-Child Interaction n.d. (Box 7)
  - Directory of Predominantly Black Colleges and Universities in the United States of America 1972 (Box 7)
  - Articles, Intelligence, Dollars a commitment to Higher Education 1970 (Box 7)
  - H.L. Walker and Associates Architects and Planners, business portfolio n.d. (Box 7)
  - Higher Education in Virginia 1973-1974, 2 copies (Box 7)
  - Higher Education in Virginia 1971 (Box 7)
  - Baptists of North America - a Fact Book 1972 (Box 7)
  - Outlook, U.S. Department of Commerce March 1972 (Box 7)
  - Minority-Owned Businesses 1969 (Box 7)
  - Higher Education Aid for Minority Business: a directory of assistance available to minorities by selected schools of business 1970 (Box 7)
  - Financing Virginia's Colleges 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - Progress of the Minority Business Enterprise Program Jan 1972 (Box 7)
  - Resident and Off-Campus Enrollment, Virginia State-Controlled Institutions of Higher Education 1971-1972 (Box 7)
  - The Excluded Student, Educational Practices Affecting Mexican Americans in the Southwest May 1972 (Box 7)
  - Accredited Post-Secondary Institutions and Programs Jan 1970 (Box 7)
  - For Our New Day centennial development program 1965 (Box 7)
  - Virginia Union University catalogue n.d. (Box 7)
  - Virginia Union University catalogue 1969-1970 (Box 7)
  - Virginia Union Bulletin, homecoming issue Oct 1969 (Box 7)
  - The South and Her Children, School Desegregation 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - Directory of Predominantly Negro Colleges and Universities in the United States of America Jan1969 (Box 7)
  - The Present Dilemma of the Negro by Kenneth B. Clark, PhD 1967 Nov 29 (Box 7)
  - Women in Higher Education by Alan Pifer 1971 Nov 29 (Box 7)
  - A Seed, Humanities Dept. 1972 (Box 7)
  - Campus Governance: the amazing thing is that it works at all, Report 11 July 1971 (Box 7)
  - Graduating Seniors Look Back at Their Freshman Year in College April 1972 (Box 7)
  - Toward More Active Learning Feb 1972 (Box 7)
  - What an Executive Should Know About His Social Responsibility 1972 (Box 7)
  - Lott Carey Herald March 1972 (Box 7)
  - The Baptist Herald May 1972 (Box 7)
- Series II
  - Academic Advisement (Box-folder 1:1)
  - Academic Alliance School College Faculty Collaboration (Box-folder 1:2)
  - Academic Coordinators (Box-folder 1:3)
  - Academic Costumes Code (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Academic Council (Box-folder 1:5)
  - Academic History (Box-folder 1:6)
  - Academic Probation and Warning (Box-folder 1:7)
  - Academic Programs (Box-folder a:8)
  - Academic Regalia (Box-folder 1:9)
  - Academic Requirements (Box-folder 1:10)
  - Academic Standing (Box-folder 1:11)
  - Academic Structure (Box-folder 1:12)
  - Accreditation (Box-folder 1:14)
  - Accreditation STVU (Box-folder 1:15)
  - Achievements (Box-folder 1:16)
  - Acres (Virginia Union University Property) (Box-folder 1:17)
  - Action Goals (Box-folder 1:18)
  - Action Items (Box-folder 1:19)
  - Action Plan for Finalizing Fiscal 84-85 (Box-folder 1:20)
  - Action Plans (Box-folder 1:21)
  - Addresses (Box-folder 1:22)
  - Administrative (confidential) (Box-folder 1:23)
  - Administrative Chart (Box-folder 1:24)
  - Administrative Memo (Box-folder 1:25)
  - Administrative Practices and Procedures (Box-folder 1:26)
  - Administrative PR Samples (Box-folder 1:27)
  - Administrative Role Responsibilities (Box-folder 1:28)
  - Administrative Staff (Box-folder 1:29)
  - Admissions Information (Box-folder 1:30)
  - Admissions in Predominantly Negro Colleges (a view from inside) (Box-folder 1:31)
  - Admissions Procedures (Box-folder 1:32)
  - Advisement (Box-folder 1:33)
  - Aerobics (class for faculty / staff) (Box-folder 1:34)
  - Aerobics Classes (Box-folder 1:35)
  - African Art Objects (president's office as of May '83) (Box-folder 1:36)
  - Agenda For Faculty Meetings (Box-folder 1:37)
  - Agreements (Box-folder 1:38)
  - Agreements (Provost, etc.) (Box-folder 1:39)
  - Alma Mater (Box-folder 1:40)
  - Alumni Addresses (Box-folder 1:41)
  - Alumni Addresses 1987 (Box-folder 1:42)
  - Alumni Association (Box-folder 1:43)
  - Alumni Association Constitution (Box-folder 1:44)
  - Alumni Athletes (Box-folder 1:45)
  - Alumni Banquets 1974 (Box-folder 1:46)
  - Alumni Banquets 1976-1980 (Box-folder 1:47)
  - Alumni Banquets 1981 (Box-folder 1:48)
  - Alumni Banquets 1982 (Box-folder 1:49)
  - Alumni Banquets 1983-1984 (Box-folder 1:50)
  - Alumni Banquets 1985 (Box-folder 1:51)
  - Alumni Banquets 1986 (Box-folder 1:52)
  - Alumni Banquets 1987 (Box-folder 1:53)
  - Alumni Banquets 1996-1997 (Box-folder 1:54)
  - Alumni - Certificates (Box-folder 1:55)
  - Alumni Chapters (Box-folder 1:56)
  - Alumni Chapters - Atlanta (Box-folder 1:57)
  - Alumni Chapters - Baltimore Area (Box-folder 1:58)
  - Alumni Chapters - Barco Chapter (Box-folder 1:59)
  - Alumni Chapter - (Birmingham, Alabama - Area) (Box-folder 1:60)
  - Alumni Chapter - Boston (Box-folder 1:61)
  - Alumni Chapter, Brown, Homer S. (Box-folder 1:62)
  - Alumni Chapter, Bunn, Benjamin F. (Box-folder 1:63)
  - Alumni Chapter - California (Box-folder 1:64)
  - Alumni Chapter - Capital Beltway (Box-folder 1:65)
  - Alumni Chapter - Caroline County (Box-folder 1:66)
  - Alumni Chapter - D.C. Area (Box-folder 1:67)
  - Alumni Chapter -Ellison - Ruffin (Box-folder 1:68)
  - Alumni Chapter -Georgia (Box-folder 1:69)
  - Alumni Chapter- Guidelines (Box-folder 1:70)
  - Alumni Chapter - Hanover (Box-folder 1:71)
  - Alumni Chapter ( letters to and from) (Box-folder 1:72)
  - Alumni Chapter -Lynchburg (Box-folder 1:73)
  - Alumni Chapter 1981 March 13-14 (Box-folder 1:74)
  - Alumni Chapter - Miles Connor (Box-folder 1:75)
  - Alumni Chapter - Miles Connor (Box-folder 1:76)
  - Alumni Chapter - New Jersey (Box-folder 1:77)
  - Alumni Chapter -Newport News (Box-folder 1:78)
  - Alumni Chapter -N.Y. (Box-folder 2:1)
  - Alumni Chapter -North Carolina (Box-folder 2:2)
  - Alumni Chapter -Ohio, Cleveland (Box-folder 2:3)
  - Alumni Chapter Organization (proposed for) (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Alumni Chapter -Portsmouth (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Alumni Chapter Presidents (Box-folder 2:6)
  - Alumni Chapter - Roanoke, VA (Box-folder 2:7)
  - Alumni Chapter (scholarships) (Box-folder 2:8)
  - Alumni Chapter Shepard (Box-folder 2:9)
  - Alumni Chapter - Storer (Box-folder 2:10)
  - Alumni Chapter- STVU (Box-folder 2:11)
  - Alumni - Chicago Area (Box-folder 2:12)
  - Alumni Choir (Box-folder 2:13)
  - Alumni Class Presidents 1919 to 1980 (Box-folder 2:13A.)
  - Alumni College Presidents (Box-folder 2:14)
  - Alumni Coordinator (Box-folder 2:15)
  - Alumni Correspondence (Box-folder 2:16)
  - Alumni Day Activities (Box-folder 2:17)
  - Alumni D.C. (Box-folder 2:18)
  - Alumni Deceased (Box-folder 2:19)
    by year
  - Alumni Directories (Box-folder 2:20)
  - Alumni Directories (Box-folder 2:21)
  - Alumni Distinguished (Box-folder 2:22)
  - Alumni Doctors (Box-folder 2:23)
  - Alumni Elected- Officials (Box-folder 2:24)
  - Executive Committee Mtg. 1982 Oct 1 (Box-folder 2:25)
  - Alumni Fifty Year (Box-folder 2:26)
  - Alumni Interesting Facts (Box-folder 2:27)
  - Alumni International Association, (1/4) (Box-folder 2:28)
  - Alumni International Association, (2/4) (Box-folder 2:29)
  - Alumni International Association, (3/4) (Box-folder 2:30)
  - Alumni International Association, (4/4) (Box-folder 2:31)
  - Alumni Leaders (Box-folder 2:32)
  - Alumni Letters (Box-folder 2:33)
  - Alumni Ministers (Box-folder 2:34)
  - Alumni Monthly Report and Communication (Box-folder 2:35)
  - Alumni National Association (Box-folder 2:36)
  - Alumni News (Box-folder 2:37)
  - Alumni Officers (Box-folder 2:38)
  - Alumni Outstanding (Box-folder 2:39)
  - Alumni Philadelphia Area (Box-folder 2:40)
  - Alumni- Philadelphia Area, Marshall Shepard (Box-folder 2:41)
  - Alumni - Pre-Alumni Club (Box-folder 2:42)
  - Alumni, Prominent (Box-folder 2:43)
  - Alumni Representatives (Box-folder 2:44)
  - Alumni- So. California Chapter (Box-folder 2:45)
  - Alumni South Carolina (Box-folder 2:46)
  - Alumni Systems (Box-folder 2:47)
  - Alumni Task Force (Box-folder 2:48)
  - Alumni Ticket Request (Box-folder 2:49)
  - Alumni- Virginia Union University Health Care Professionals (Box-folder 2:50)
  - Alumni Weekend (Box-folder 2:51)
  - Alumni West Virginia (Box-folder 2:52)
  - Alumni Who served as College Presidents (Box-folder 2:53)
  - Alumni Workshop (Box-folder 2:54)
  - Alumnus of Year (Box-folder 2:55)
  - Amity Aides (Box-folder 3:1)
  - Analytical Studies Team (Box-folder 3:2)
  - Announcements (Box-folder 3:3)
  - Annual Fund 1994 (Box-folder 3:4)
  - Annual Reports (Box-folder 3:5)
  - Appeals (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Appeals Board Nominations (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Articulation Manual (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Assemblies (Box-folder 3:9)
  - Assessment and Improvement of the Academic Skills for Entering the Freshmen Students (Box-folder 3:10)
  - Association of Official Personnel (Box-folder 3:11)
  - Assumptions (Box-folder 3:12)
  - Attendance (Box-folder 3:13)
  - Audit 1997 (Box-folder 3:14)
  - Audit and Budget (Box-folder 3:15)
  - Audit Reports Sent (Box-folder 3:16)
  - Audits (Box-folder 3:17)
  - Automobile Registration (Box-folder 3:18)
  - Award of Merit (Box-folder 3:19)
  - Awards (Box-folder 3:20)
  - Awards Luncheon (Box-folder 3:21)
  - Baccalaureate, (1/2) (Box-folder 3:22)
  - Baccalaureate, (2/2) (Box-folder 3:23)
  - Band (Box-folder 3:24)
  - Bankruptcy (Box-folder 3:25)
  - Banks (Box-folder 3:26)
  - Bids (Box-folder 3:27)
  - Biographical Data Forms (Box-folder 3:28)
  - Black History Month (Box-folder 3:29)
  - Blue Ribbon Task Force, (1/3) (Box-folder 3:30)
  - Blue Ribbon Task Force, (2/3) (Box-folder 3:31)
  - Blue Ribbon Task Force, (3/3) (Box-folder 3:32)
  - Boosters Club, (1/3) (Box-folder 3:33)
  - Boosters Club, (2/3) (Box-folder 3:34)
  - Boosters Club, (3/3) (Box-folder 3:35)
  - Boosters Club Receipt Report (Box-folder 3:36)
  - Brother John (Box-folder 3:37)
  - Brown, Homer Memorial Room (Box-folder 3:38)
  - Brown, Homer Museum (Box-folder 3:39)
  - Buck and the Preacher (Box-folder 3:40)
  - Building Program (Box-folder 3:41)
  - Building Valuation (Box-folder 3:42)
  - Bulletin Information (Box-folder 3:43)
  - Business Majors 1989 (Box-folder 3:44)
  - Busts (Afro-American) (Box-folder 3:45)
  - Bylaws (Box-folder 3:46)
  - Cabinet Membership (Box-folder 3:47)
  - Calendar (Academic)
  - Calendar of Events (Box-folder 4:1)
  - Calendar Info (Box-folder 4:2)
  - Calendar (Management) (Box-folder 4:3)
  - Calendar (Masks) 1983-1984 (Box-folder 4:4)
  - Campus Informer (Box-folder 4:5)
  - Campus Life (Box-folder 4:6)
  - Campus Projects (Box-folder 4:7)
  - Candidates for Graduation (Box-folder 4:8)
  - Capital Campaign Packet (Box-folder 4:9)
  - Capital Improvements (Box-folder 4:10)
  - Capital Programs (Box-folder 4:11)
  - Career Emphasis Week (Box-folder 4:12)
  - Case Statement (Box-folder 4:13)
  - Cash Flow (Box-folder 4:14)
  - Catalog Distribution (Box-folder 4:15)
  - Catalogue, (1/2) (Box-folder 4:16)
  - Catalogue, (2/2) (Box-folder 4:17)
  - Catalouge Request (Box-folder 4:18)
  - Census Date (Box-folder 4:19)
  - Center for Black Enterprise (Box-folder 4:20)
  - Center for Community Education (Box-folder 4:21)
  - Central Reproduction Center (Box-folder 4:22)
  - Certificate of Deposit (Box-folder 4:23)
  - Certification of Teachers (Box-folder 2:24)
  - Chairs (Box-folder $:25)
  - Challenge (Box-folder 4:26)
  - Chancellor (Box-folder 2:27)
  - Chapel (Box-folder 4:28)
  - Charts, (1/2) (Box-folder 4:29)
  - Charts, (2/2) (Box-folder 4:30)
  - Check List for Volunteers Soliciting Big Gifts (Box-folder 4:31)
  - Check Signer (Box-folder 4:32)
  - Cheerleaders (Box-folder 4:33)
  - Choir (Box-folder 4:34)
  - Choir Robes (Box-folder 4:35)
  - Choir Tours (Box-folder 4:36)
  - Choral Concerts, (1/3) (Box-folder 4:37)